Hi. My name's Wendy.
嗨, 我是Wendy.
Can I get you something to drink?
我可以给你们拿点喝的吗?
We need a bottle of mineral water
我们需要一瓶矿泉水
and a carafe of the house red wine.
和一大瓶(carafe)自制红葡萄酒
Sorry. Are you ready to order?
抱歉. 你们准备好点菜了吗?
Yes, I think so.
是的, 我想是的.
Would you like an appetizer?
你们想要一个开胃菜吗?
Yes. What was the starter, Richard?
是的. (刚才看到的)那个开胃菜是什么, Richard?
Yes. We'd like one spare ribs to share, please.
是的. 我们要一份排骨分着吃, 请.
Fine. And for your main course?
好的. 对于你们的主菜呢?
Yes. I'd like the roast chicken
是的. 我要点烤鸡
with roast potatoes and vegetables.
带上烤土豆和蔬菜.
Excuse me!
抱歉
No problem.
没关系
And for you?
你呢?
I'd like the soup and salad.
我要点汤和沙拉.
What kind of soup?
哪一种汤?
Tomato soup, please.
西红柿汤, 请.
Oh, now I'm doing it.
Oh, 现在我也在做了(打哈欠).
I'm sorry. I was up all night.
不好意思. 我一宿没睡昨晚.
My dog was sick.
我的狗狗生病了.
Oh. How sad.
Oh. 多令人伤心.
He's better today. But I'm exhausted.
他今天好多了. 但是我累坏了.
Aren't we all!
我们难道不都是嘛!